EU B-ORG
rejects O
the O
call O
of O
Germany B-LOC
to O
boycott O
lamb O
from O
Great B-LOC
Britain I-LOC
. O

China B-LOC
says O
time O
right O
for O
Taiwan B-LOC
talks O
. O



# The source text is tokenized and tagged. For each token, there is a tag with BIO markup. Tags are separated from tokens with whitespaces. Sentences are separated with empty lines.